Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every wall that's
in our wake, go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little
more To get to the answers we're
looking for We came to this new world
believing That surely someday we
just might find the way All the
pieces of our dreams have now come
together Our bonds won't waver With
our dreaming hand Let's head on towards
A bright new future Now
everybody lift your hands up
Sing about what you are dreaming
Always stand up Raise up
the flag that you believe in
Gotta keep up We'll get past
everyone that's in our way
Let's head on never stopping
Only look up Keep your head up way up
high Always step up If waves are rough,
jump to the sky Never give up Our wishes,
they will come together And
lead us on for the future
We drift on riding the
waves Towards another
shore day by day There are many meetings,
many goodbyes Underneath the flag we fly
I'll remember the pain within I'll keep
it in my heart forever And never take it
lightly But I won't surrender This freedom
I will keep in mind I'll keep holding on,
never stop it Now everybody
lift your hands up Sing
about what you are dreaming
Always stand up Raise
up the flag that you believe
in Gotta keep up We'll
get past everyone that's
in our way Let's head on,
never stop it
Only look up, keep your head
up way up high Always step up,
if brains are rough, jump
to the sky Never give up,
our wishes they will come together
And lead us on for the future
Hands up
hey what the hell was that for
listen huh he was talking I
heard him yeah I think the heat's
getting to you pal I don't know
maybe it is even a dragon it
could be something way more
dangerous this sure looks like
one though doesn't it it It does,
that's a dragon for sure.
A lizard-like body with massive wings.
That's exactly the way dragons
are described in all the myths.
Uh-oh!
So it can breathe fire, too!
Yeah!
Ah!
I don't know what I was
expecting, but come on really.
Bring it on!
Now, Gum-Gum!
Jet bullet!
Oh, no! Huh?
You got some thick skin, huh?
Look! Behind you!
Whoa!
It sees us!
You're mine!
Patty!
I can sense your presence!
Here!
Oh, I see now.
Luffy was right, that
thing really can talk.
Dreeshort style...
Ultra Tiger Trap!
Damn it!
This guy is one stubborn lizard!
Back off!
Luffy! Huh?
I heard him talk too.
I told ya!
Yeah, I heard it too! But how?
Oh, great!
Now he's flying!
Patty!
Are you also allies of the Seven Warlords?
It's hot!
It worse than that!
Talking Dragon!
He mentioned the Seven Warlords,
so could he be an enemy of theirs?
Luffy, just leave this blowhard to me.
I'll cut him to pieces in no time.
Sure, go ahead.
But first...
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Let me bring him to you.
It feels like he's on fire, too!
Huh?
Patty!
I feel a breeze all of
a sudden. How curious!
Huh?
The flames are nipping at my tender flesh.
Have mercy!
The tickles! Patty!
Stand down!
Such dishonorable behavior!
Ha!
I was right!
Hey, guys!
You won't believe this!
There's some weird fancy pants guy
stuck in the dragon's back! Huh?
What the hell is he talking about?
That means the voice we've
been hearing must be...
All right, that's enough!
Eat this if you're hungry!
Hehehe!
Hehehehe!
Stupid!
Hey!
Heads up!
Huh?
Usopp!
You got it!
Special attack, Green Star!
Trampolia!
One-sword style!
E .I.
Death Lion Song, you're done.
Yeah!
Zoro!
I bet this thing is delicious!
There's enough fire around to barbecue it!
Now you're talking!
Here, see any floor.
Nummies one!
A cold crepe to go with
the shellfish just for you!
I got some champagne, too! Huh?
Uh, are you guys sleeping?
It's foggy.
That's not fog, damn I
already inhaled some of it.
It's some kind of sleeping gas.
Is this just a normal
occurrence in the new world?
Or did somebody sneak onto the ship?
I hope the rest of the crew took a baby
transponder snail to the island with them.
I have to find a way to tell them.
we've got two humans one
cyborg and some sort of pet
tie them all up right right it's a
good thing they're just low-life pirates
so no one's even going to
miss them how convenient
The master will be pleased with this.
Pull him out!
Hurt!
Unhand me, you ruffling!
How dare you! Hey!
I'm trying to help you here!
Stop squirming!
Come on!
I broke him! Sorry!
Sorry is all you have to say!
He's dead now!
Oh, seems I've been liberated.
What?
He's still alive and his legs can talk?
It's a monster!
A zombie!
Wait a second.
There's no upper body anywhere.
Nor is there a mark on the
dragon where he was stuck. Huh?
Yeah, I don't get it.
So, then the guy was just legs all along?
Ugh, this is pretty weird, huh?
Huh, he looks kind of big.
I know you were there, but I
cannot discern your intent.
With neither eyes nor ears, I
can only sense your presence.
Wow, you're smart!
Well, for legs...
Root!
Whoever you are, get out of my way!
Calm down!
I refuse to die in a place like this!
I have a mission to carry out!
He's running away!
I will not suffer this indignity!
Prepare yourself, Warlord!
I'm coming for you!
Hey, wait!
Lex, come and join my crowd!
You cut that out!
Weird.
So how does that work?
Beats me.
Nice job.
This dragon's good.
By the way, what do you
call people like this?
Huh? Um...
With four legs?
A centaur, I guess.
I'm a centaur!
This is awesome!
Why do these legs keep getting stuck?
First a dragon, now Luffy?
We're a team now!
Curses!
I seem to have affixed myself to
something again. Boot! Cease this!
Luffy, that's vulgar. Stop.
You think so?
Just cause he's stuck to you
doesn't mean he has to listen.
He's probably got his own head
calling the shot somewhere.
Let him go and maybe he'll find it.
Mr.
Sticky Legs was born like this.
Duh.
You need to get with the program, Usopp,
right? Come on. That's ridiculous.
Hey, are you coming with us or what?
I wonder if he's got a real name.
By the way,
since you're the only one who's
going to be eating all this meat,
why don't you carry it?
Get the legs to help.
Hey, come up here.
I found something weird. Yeah?
Any clues about the
samurai or the other dude?
Look.
What now?
Snow!
There's snow on those mountains!
Actually, I think those are glaciers.
Everything's on fire over here, but the
other side of the lake is frozen solid?
I could go for some cool weather
right now, but this is ridiculous.
How did it get like this?
That solves one mystery,
at least. Like what?
Oh, wait!
Why that guy said he was cold, you mean?
Someone help!
What's wrong? Please! It's cold!
We need boss!
My friends are getting cut
down, one after another!
The samurai is gonna kill us!
So then, if we want to find the samurai
and the other guy, we have to switch sides.
Wow, this place is fun.
We can cross that lake, right?
I'm getting hot.
I want to make snow cones.
Get real.
We'd freeze to death over there.
The lake's too big.
Let's go back for now. Cold, huh?
That's not much better.
We'll be fine.
If we can find some wild animals,
we can skin them and make coats.
You're nuts.
The only thing we'll find
over there is ice cubes.
Perfect for snow cones.
Wait, can't we talk this over, Luffy?
What the hell?
There was a bird, only it
was also a human somehow.
I don't know, it was weird.
The point is, this island is full of
monsters and they're gonna eat us for sure.
Look, there's nothing there.
Oh, Sanji, what's all
this kicking about, man?
Good, you're up.
Can't you see for yourself?
They locked us up, Franky!
We're done for, I tell you!
We're done for!
Huh? Huh?
Hey!
What the heck happened?
What is this freaky place?
I know, I was eating dessert
on the deck of the Sunny,
and then I, I don't remember anything.
None of us do; we must have
been hit with sleeping gas,
then when we passed out, someone must
have dragged us off to this place.
No way—I do remember the ship
getting hit with some kind of gas.
I'm sorry if I'd noticed it
sooner; we wouldn't be here.
here
We can't break out, huh?
Maybe they want to sell us
his slaves or suck our blood.
If they took everyone on the sunny,
then what happened to Brooke?
I don't know.
It was just us when we woke up.
It's because he's a skeleton.
He doesn't have any blood
to drink, so they left him.
Do you think they'll drink my cola too?
Both of you!
Shut up!
May I speak?
Wait, who is that?
Sure, wasn't me?
Show yourself, bro!
I know not from where you hail.
But if you're proficient in puzzles?
I have one in the form of my head.
I think this thing is talking to us.
But what the heck is it?
I am no thing
Is it a bug?
But it talks.
Like a transponder snail?
We're outnumbered.
There are eight of them.
I'm no insect either.
That aside, it appears that you
people are trustworthy enough.
What you see on the floor
are pieces of my face.
I beg of you, please put
them back together for me.
Your face?
Wait, I see.
It's a mouth.
And an eye.
How's this?
There. Done.
Yeah, that's a face.
You left out a fair
number of parts, though.
Let me try.
Better?
This doesn't feel right.
No, no, no.
Watch, this is how you do it.
I dig that.
I don't at all.
Oh, let me try.
This is my face.
It's not a toy.
Help me!
I got it.
Looking pretty human, bro.
I believe my chin and hair may still
be somewhat awry, but it's good enough.
I'm grateful.
It's a severed head! Clearly.
Wait, are you a ghost?
How can you talk?
I wish I knew that.
A swordsman cut me into many pieces.
That villain, he used
some manner of sorcery.
He severed my limbs, but I did not bleed.
I did not die.
I was denied a warrior's death.
Instead, I suffered this indignity.
I'm a disgrace.
One, two, three.
Three.
Four intruders.
Well, did you find them?
Yeah, they're right here.
I've got all four of them in my sights.
I'll take them out. Don't worry.
I see.
You have fun with that.
Give me a ring when you're
done, all right? Roger.
So this guy cut you you're
still alive even without a body.
That's crazy
It's like buggy creepy
Under different circumstances, I'd
slit my belly and die and mourned.
But alas, there's something that I must
do, even if I'm forced to live in disgrace!
Hold on.
Old man, can you tell us
anything about this place?
Old man, you say?
You need to show some respect, you woman!
I'm a proud warrior, you know.
Where I'm from, women are
chaste, and they are modest.
They walk three steps behind the men. Huh?
Too bad. I don't care.
You're just a head. Be grateful.
We easily could have kept
you in pieces on the floor.
Unhand me, you damn harlot!
Wow, you really don't get it, do you?
I said unhand me! Curse you!
Is this proper, where you come from?
I've never suffered such rudeness.
However, it seems your clothes
were torn from your body,
so perhaps I should be more sympathetic.
I chose this outfit myself,
thank you very much. What?
Sorry, but I look good.
Your attire is obscene.
All you're wearing is a breast band.
You like it, don't you?
Yes, indeed I do.
I know that look!
You pervert!
That was a trap!
You must have cracked your skull!
That looks painful! Yes! No!
I mean, uh, it's fine.
It barely tickles.
I see.
So a breast band is
appropriate in your land.
I approve.
I don't care what you think!
Please, just answer me one thing.
Who are you people?
I heard our captors say that
you were seized from a ship.
Yeah, that's right.
We're pirates.
You're pirates?
If only I had known sooner!
I loathe pirates!
Though I should have guessed!
That does explain your barbarism!
In this frozen hell, I thought
we were all victims of fate.
so I had hoped that we
could escape together.
Alas, it shan't be so!
Huh?
Wait, you lost me here!
What do you mean frozen?
This place is so hot,
even the sea is on fire.
Yeah, there was lava and everything.
We were sweating just on the boat.
Aha, I see.
Old man?
Did you see the volcano here?
Or feel an eruption?
Something like that?
I did hear a loud explosion.
But both the island and the
sea surrounding it were frozen.
And that is the last
thing I shall say to you.
Cursed pirates!
The sky.
I thought it looked strange.
I could tell even from the boat.
The flaming side that Luffy and the
others went to is only half of the island.
The people that grabbed us took us to
the other side, which is frozen solid.
We need to get out of this room.
I don't care how.
Then we'll find out what's going on here.
I get what you're saying, but I kicked it
pretty hard, and that door isn't budding.
Step aside! Huh?
My cola is maxed out!
Whoa, whoa, that's a big one!
Ranking Radical Bee!
Let's move, brother! Damn, Franky.
Should have led with that one.
Sometimes I wish I was a cyborg, too!
So what are you gonna do?
Last chance.
You'd rather sit there on the
floor than associate with pirates?
Silence! Leave me be!
So what?
Are you gonna roll out of here
and bite your way to freedom?
Let me go!
Well, Samurai, tell me!
What? Samurai? For real?
This topknot is a traditional
hairstyle in the land of Wano.
So, he's the one who killed those guys?
Does that mean he might kill us?
Or bite us? No!
What was that explosion?
I have no idea.
Do you think it was those pirates?
Hey, they're coming.
Let's hurry.
We came here because we received a
distress call from one of your victims.
You got a story you
want to tell us, or not?
Sanji, come on! Leave him here!
He's our enemy!
I swear, I would not disgrace
myself by killing in cold blood!
I'm here to save my son's life, and I
would cut down anyone who stands in my way!
There!
Don't let them get away!
Those are my friends!
Cut it out, will ya?
Weapons left!
You're kidding me!
How did they get out of that room?
I don't know, but we'd
better call the master.
What the hell do they want from us?
Dawn!
Wait a sec!
You brought the head? Why?
It'll work out. Leave him to me.
There's a door!
What?
Who are you?
Hello there, kids.
What?
There's children?
They're so big.
I guess they're giants.
But are we in prison or daycare?
They're the biggest I've ever seen.
Did we drop anchor on an island of giants?
No, because they're are
regular-sized children, too.
Okay, then it's some kind
of all-inclusive nursery?
There aren't any adults here to
supervise, though, Mocha, who are they?
I've never seen them before.
You must be the ones who are frozen.
How did you escape frozen?
What is she talking about?
Robots, huh?
Whoa, are you okay?
Oh man, these tykes really love me!
And it's all because
of my armored physique!
What did she mean by the
ones who were frozen?
Look, a plushie!
A stuffed raccoon!
I'm a reindeer, okay? Too tiny!
And cute! Yeah! Help! They got me!
Close call.
Sure glad they're not interested in me.
Look!
His eyebrow's curly!
Shut up, small fry!
It's freaky!
That's it! I've had enough!
Do you know a child named Momonosuke?
I am looking for my boy!
I'm scared!
I don't have to talk!
Hey!
Don't go!
We've got questions about the...
Come back here!
Hey! Shut up!
We're trying to get
information out of them!
And they won't talk if you scare them!
The door to the biscuit room is open.
They're coming for us.
Let's get moving.
It must be those pirates.
We can't let them get away.
What kind of facility is this place?
You've got to tell us!
You must aid me in my
search for Momonosuke!
I thought we told you
to keep your mouth shut!
I've been disgraced as a samurai!
All because I was
attacked by a woman! What?
Oh, quit your whining, you chauvinist pig!
I knew it was them! I got them.
No, wait!
Hold your fire!
We can't use guns or explosives, and
let's keep the gas grenades to a minimum.
The master would be furious if we
were to hurt one of the children.
Be good, little boys and
girls, and stay out of our way.
If you don't, you might get hurt.
It's dangerous, kids.
Hey, Mr.
Robot, did you come
from outside the island?
Yep, I sure did, buddy.
But let's be clear, I'm really a cyborg.
Do you have a ship, right?
Do we ever?
It's called the Sunny. It's
the best. Then save us. Huh?
What does he mean by that?
You have to. Please. What do you mean?
Take your kids with us?
This place isn't a daycare after all.
No, don't leave.
Don't leave us here.
We're not sick anymore. We're
better. Promise. What's that?
They were sick?
Damn it, they're in the way!
Don't leave us behind!
We need you to help us get out of here!
Please, you're our only
help of getting home!
Now, now, children, you need to calm down.
Kids, I'm sorry, but we've got to go!
They want to come.
I think we should take them with us.
What?
Are you crazy?
We don't even know how we're
going to save ourselves.
Look, even if we made it back to
the ship, there's too many of them.
This sucks.
Something bad's going to happen.
Promise me!
You'll come back later and rescue us!
I know what's out there!
I've never been outside of this
building before, but I know!
There's nothing else on
this island, is there?
There are no cities!
No people either!
Because nobody came to help us!
I want to go home and see
my mommy and daddy again!
You can leave now!
But you have to come back!
You're the only ones who can save us!
That's it.
We're not leaving them.
What the hell's gotten into you?
We don't even know if they need saving!
They told us they're sick!
For all we know, this could be a hospital!
We've just met these kids.
We don't know who they
are, why they're here.
It's not our job to
help everybody. We meet?
I understand that Sanji
and I know it's risky,
but there's no way that I can
turn my back on these children.
Not when we are they're
only hope of getting help.
We've got to do something and fast.
Those brats are in the way.
Who cares?
Go ahead and shoot them too.
But the master will?
He'll be angry.
He'll be angrier if they escape!
Nice one, son, to eat
their butts, Billy Browse!
Diabless Shambi Collier Strike!
Wow, cool!
Impressive.
That fellow is very strong. Aw, damn.
Wow!
That's called Kung-Fu Point.
Look at that! Wahoo! Ah!
Ah!
Way to go, Raccoon!
And now it's my turn!
Strong right!
Rocket Punch, go!
What are we supposed to do now?
They stopped running from us.
She's so sweet, huh?
Let's be honest.
She's only sweet to kids, but that's okay.
Just makes her sexier.
Okay, Chopper.
Take Nami and get out of here.
Right, I'll protect her. Wahoo!
Listen up, ankle biters.
Follow the beautiful lady
and the Kong fu raccoon.
I'll fight the guys who are chasing us.
Let's get one thing straight.
I'm not doing any of this for you.
I'm just trying to help Nami carry
out her beautiful act of kindness.
If anything, I hate you
for putting her in danger.
And because she likes you so much.
Thanks for helping us, curly brow guy.
Start running! Hurry up!
You're just wasting time!
Cause it's going down!
Remarkable.
They were able to penetrate my
impenetrable door. Huh? Master!
This burn mark, it looks like
it was caused by a laser.
I thought that Dr.
Vegapunk's pacifistas were the
only things with that power.
At any rate, whoever these intruders
are, they're not to be trifled with.
That being said, I assume you
haven't recaptured them yet.
Last I heard, they were corralling
them into the biscuit room.
Hmm.
I suppose that could work.
Master, are you there? Huh?
Yes, go ahead.
A navy ship is approaching
the northwest shore.
It looks like they're with G5.
What should we do?
Turn them away and do it quickly.
Throw out some poison gas.
They'll get the idea,
but be certain not to kill them We
wouldn't want to start any trouble.
Yes, sir
You said there's ice and snow.
Indeed there is.
See when I awoke to find
the ship in that condition.
It was quite a shock chilling
bone You might say wait,
I mean a chill boning shocker No,
it's chock-shocking something.
Never mind!
Oh, darn it! Okay, wait.
You said there were these guys
on the sunny when you woke up.
Who were they?
I...
forgot to ask.
Probably should have
questioned them first.
Oh, well. Pity.
Terribly sorry.
I don't know a thing.
They're all wearing gas masks and
have tanks on their backs, though.
A gas mask? Huh.
They likely use some sort of chemical
weapon to knock everyone out.
Then, in the meantime, they move the Sunny
over to the other side of the island.
Damn, you beat me!
You're too fast!
Well, your legs aren't
built for running like mine.
Okay, round two, come on!
Suit yourself, but...
Hello?
What the hell are you doing?
Sorry, I can't find them You
sure the intruders are nearby?
I got nothing.
There's a guy, though.
He's got talking legs, but he's one of us.
No, he's not, you moron!
Something wrong?
I'm ready to do this what but the others I
do worry if they didn't
leave a note there's
only one answer they
were taken by those men
in masks right and they
didn't take you because
you look dead until you woke up instead of
feeling unwanted I suppose
I should feel grateful
I might send help let's
be quick look around
see anything like a
building or you scarcely
need me at all Robin
it's like you can see it
yourself
there
is and
it's massive it's not a
restaurant i know that
much keep a low profile
we'll get there as soon
as possible roger oh
robin while i've got you on what kind of
panties are you think
these guys work for the
government who knows but
they're human So I guess
that's better than what
we've been getting here.
A fire-breathing dragon?
A pair of talking legs?
Some bird woman?
Plus, that centaur guy
Luffy made friends with.
Speaking of...
Try to trick me, will you? What? No, stop!
I thought you were one of us.
We were friends a second ago.
You're the one who started
swinging that club.
Don't blame me.
You're finished, sucker!
Luffy, careful!
All right then, let me.
Snow Fleur!
Bellflower!
Giraffes? What's next?
Guess there's all kinds of
centaurs out there, huh?
That's funny.
It is not funny.
These guys are monsters and
they're trying to kill you!
Look, he's got one, too.
And it says CC on it.
They're not just free-roaming
magical creatures.
They're part of some organization.
What's worse, even if we tried to
get out of here, the Sunny is gone.
All we can do now is go to the frozen
side of the island and find Brooke.
Chopper, Nami, Sanji, Franky.
We've lost them all.
It is troubling.
They were all taken by those men in masks.
If they're passed out, the enemy
could kill them at any time they like.
Don't say that!
What a mess.
We did this all wrong.
Everything's happening on the frozen side.
We did fine.
I got to eat that big
dragon, and I met Dr.
Leggingston, too.
Did you say Leggingston?
That's what I named my new back leg.
Forget the snow cones.
It's a rescue mission.
And since I can't run away...
Guess I'm gonna fight.
Well, I hope they sell
warm coats over there.
And more likely, we'll
just all freeze to death.
It was nice knowing you.
The men are in danger, Vice Admiral.
I can't breathe.
This gas is everywhere.
This got messy already.
What a dangerous place.
In case you hadn't heard, Dr.
Vegapunk used to test his
chemical weapons on this island.
Then, they shut the operation
down four years ago.
If Straw Hat's here, I sure as
heck don't see his pirate ship.
Besides, the island's been a
hellhole since the accident.
No one can survive out there.
I don't buy it.
It's been too long and
there's too much gas.
I don't understand, sir!
Two years ago, there was no
sea of fire or sea of ice.
It was just a deserted island.
The toxic substances from the accident
were already cleared out as well.
They had to be, otherwise Aokiji and
Akainu wouldn't have held their duel here.
This island is the mark of their battle.
A struggle so great that the earth, the
sky, and the sea itself were transformed.